Powertron !
Special Attack !
Curses ! I 'll get you next time , Powertron !
Hold it , Kingburg !
Dammit ! Did he get away ?
However , we Powertrons will uphold the peace of the network !
Yeah !
That was nothing like the stuff on TV .
That was so cheap !
Man , that 's like way too expensive .
Like I said , it 's from that show in Hiroshima .
The one I couldn 't go to ?
When Rei went fumbling her song ' coz those guys started trouble ...
And this is the MiniDisc from when Mima sang in Rei 's place .
It 's a precious sample of Mimarin 's singing voice !
Oh , yeah ... Is that rumor true ?
Oh , that ?
Three left , only three left ...
Last issue of CHAMMINGBIRD ... only three left .
400 yen ... 400 yen ...
Yeah , I read about that too .
I heard she 's announcing it today coz it 's the last concert here .
At a nothing show like this ? That 's pretty cold of Mimarin !
There 's been lots of solo activity going on lately ...
And only Mimarin 's like worthy of being an actress ?
Look , they 're back .
The guys that caused trouble last week .
I just hope they don 't make a mess today , of all days .
I 'm getting nervous !
Come on , sit still !
Hey , what 's up with this ! ? This is all frayed !
Don 't look at me !
- Get me some masking tape ! - Hello ? Yes .
Remember your entrance in the second song , Mima !
Don 't pressure me !
I need a drink !
- I 'm sorry . I 'll call you back . - You can have drinks after the event .
You 're on !
And it looks like they 're set .
Without further adieu , please welcome to our stage ... CHAM !
Got a question about your love ?
Send a cry for help and wait a bit .
Love makes your heart race .
If it means you 're loved in the end ...
be much more aggressive ...
because you will get a chance .
The angel of love smiles at you .
Mima ! Mima ! Mima !
Mima should be acting , not singing !
I can 't do this after all !
Mika ...
They want her in a drama series .
There are no better deals than this !
She can act AND sing ! That should be all right !
Her schedule with the other two is already starting to mismatch !
She didn 't go through those hard lessons to become an actress !
The TV producer praised Mima 's acting !
But what about MIMA 'S feelings ! ?
And wait a bit .
Love makes your heart race .
If it means you 're loved in the end ...
be much more aggressive ...
because you will get a chance .
The angel of love smiles at you .
Thank you very much .
It was a fun concert , but we only have one song left ...
We just got here !
Umm ... Before our last song , we have news to tell you ...
Um , I , Mima Kirigoe , had a fun time as a member of CHAM ...
Out of the way !
What did we do ! ? HUH ! ?
Quit showin ' off ! You 're only a part-timer !
Outta my face , ya asshole !
YOU get out of here !
What the hell ! ? Who are you telling to leave , you fucker ! ?
It wasn 't me !
What are you doing ! ? Get the hell over here , whoever threw that !
Go home ! Go home !
- Dammit ! - Go home ! Go home ! Go home ! Go home !
Them again !
We 're canceling the show !
But today is !
Shut up ! Goddammit !
Go home ! Go home ! Go home ! Go home !
Stop it !
Today ...
Just today ... I wanted to have a good time with all of you !
What attitude from some no-namer !
You little ! ?
What do you want , you freak ?
Let 's go !
A-Actually ... as of today , I ...
As of today , Mima will graduate from CHAM !
- What ! ? - Why ?
Thank you all .
I 'm really happy that I spent the last 2 1 / 2 years with you all as part of CHAM !
I hope you 'll support me as I do my best as a rookie actress .
So this will be my last song . Please listen .
Well , it totally makes sense from the agency 's point of view .
Pop idols just don 't make money ... right ?
Metamorphosis , huh ?
I still remember well ...
that warmth you 'd given me .
It was in the gentle rays of sunlight .
I had believed that ...
the days past when ...
we were in love , were everything .
Now , embraced by the memories ...
I have become a coward .
I am choosing to live a life that ...
I can 't feel any ...
- Mimarin ! - Don 't leave us ! Don 't quit !
Mimarin ! Mimarin !
Thank you .
I 'm always looking at Mima 's Room !
Geez ! This cheese already went bad !
I 'm sorry ... I forgot to feed you yesterday .
The earthquake that happened in Mie prefecture ...
flattened towns throughout the region .
The government reports 200 dead , but the total number of victims are ...
yet to be determined since many more are missing amid the rubble .
Authorities have called in troops for rescue operations ...
however , because the area is already getting dark ...
Thanks for all the work over the years .
Bye bye , Mima the pop idol .
" Sing for us forever " ...
I really can 't do that .
" I always like looking into Mima 's Room . I 've put up a link to Mima 's Room . "
What is this ?
- Hello ? - Mima ! You 're home !
Mom !
Yeah , I 'm fine ! How are you ?
Really ?
Yeah . Today was the last one . No more singing for me .
I remember when you kept saying you wanted to be a singer .
This is my big chance ! I told you that already !
Lately , we 've all been looking forward to each new single !
Your uncle over in Yamaguchi buys 20 copies every time !
You just don 't understand this industry , Mom .
Wasn 't singing what you were best at ?
The pop idol image is suffocating me !
Besides , nowadays pop idols are ...
Wait , I 've got a call on the other line ...
Yes , Kirigoe here ...
Hello ?
Mom ? Just a wrong number .
Yeah , I know .
Oh , wait ! The bath !
Call me back in five minutes .
Oh , Mother !
A fax ? Who 's it from ?
Traitor traitor traltor TRAiTor TrAltoR TralTor
Who are you ?
" Who are you ? "
Do you know what that note means , Rumi ?
It 's an Internet home page .
Oh , that thing that 's been popular lately !
And what is it ?
How can I describe it ?
It 's kind of like computer networks .
And ?
Considering that this person " put up a link to Mima 's Room " ...
this " Mima 's Room " thing is the title of a web site .
You don 't get it , do you ?
Nope . Not one bit .
All right !
Sorry to keep you waiting .
We 're ready for the take !
Don 't make me laugh !
You 're laughing on your own !
5 seconds !
4 , 3 , 2 ...
The younger sister of Rika , the murder victim , is here .
Would you like to see her ?
Mr. Yamashiro .
Do you know why the culprit peels off the skin of his victims ?
I assume he gets sexual stimulation from such activities ...
- He wants to become one . - Become ... what ?
A woman ... or ...
CUT !
Eri Ochiai is a great actress after all !
She 's a completely different person when the camera is rolling !
That 's good !
NEXT ! Scene 32 !
Rika 's sister , you 're on !
Here !
Hold this !
Nervous ?
A bit .
Not much to get nervous about when you have only one line ...
How 's our star actress ?
Mr. Tadokoro . She 's just going on now .
" Who are you ? "
" Who ... "
That 's what I mean !
Good morning !
Morning !
Good morning .
Hello , everyone .
Mr. Shibuya ! You 're here too ?
Hi , Eri . How 's it going ?
Sir , your lines are too hard ! I don 't want to do it anymore !
Don 't say that !
But the story is really good ! I love stuff like this !
You 're good at egging people on !
Eri . There were this many fan letters sent to the station !
Thank you , Mr. Tejima .
Kuro ...
Oh , this one 's not for you .
Well , keep up the good work .
So , Sir , tell me !
Who 's the criminal ?
Sorry , can 't tell you . That 'd spoil the fun .
So what ARE you going to do about the criminal ?
You 're gonna have to make your mind up soon .
Good morning , Mr. Tejima ! Mr. Shibuya !
Oh , hello there ...
Mima 's getting good reviews . Even among station staff .
If that 's the case , don 't you think she 's got too few lines ?
So he says , Shibuya .
Hey , don 't look at me !
Sir ! Please ! Make use of Mima just a little bit more !
But see ... She 's a pop idol , right ?
They 're really hard to use ...
That 's no problem ! She 's done with being a pop idol !
Really ?
We want to give her a drastic image change , too .
We 're ready for the take !
Oh , this is for Mima .
" Who are you ? "
5 seconds !
4 , 3 , 2 ...
Mr. Tadokoro ! ?
Mr. Tadokoro !
I 'm all right ...
What the hell is this ! ?
I think that letter just exploded ! ?
Call an ambulance ! An ambulance !
Yes !
Is a warning . The next one will be REAL .
We 're all set now .
Rumi , you 're really amazing !
I 'll sign you up for online services now .
Okay .
What do you think , Rumi ?
About what ?
About that thing the other day .
Oh , that ...
Credit card number ...
Shouldn 't we have called the police ?
Mr. Tadokoro said not to . We can 't do anything about it .
But it was a crime !
And it might have been me !
It 's okay . It was just a prank .
Fortunately , Mr. Tadokoro wasn 't badly hurt .
So you shouldn 't worry , Mima .
Anyway , Mima , I 'll explain all of this so listen carefully .
Okay !
This is a browser for the World Wide Web .
You launch it by double-clicking here .
Wha ? Double-clip ?
What are you going to do with a clip ?
But ...
See , next to " location " you enter the URL .
It 's not hard , is it ?
Come on , Rumi !
Can 't you explain it to me in Japanese ?
Boy ! Why did you buy a computer when you don 't know anything about it ?
Because they said it was easy !
Oh , all right . I 'll explain it from the beginning once more ...
Okay !
H ... T ... T ... P ...
Ooh , something came up !
Hey , I 'm doing pretty well !
And now ...
There it is !
Mima 's Room
Mima 's Diary
Mima 's Diary What 's this ?
" It was just terrible ! "
" I screwed up the choreography , AND forgot my lyrics . "
" I feel so sorry to all my fans ! "
" This morning , when I got off the train left foot first ... "
" was when all the bad stuff started . "
" I always make it a point that my right foot ... "
" goes first into the train and into the bath . "
Someone sure knows me ! What 's this ?
" Today was my 21st birthday . "
" Yukiko , Rei , and the staff at the agency held a party for me . It was terrific ! "
" Coming home , I went grocery shopping at the usual store . "
" I got mineral water and milk . "
" The milk just has to be Cow Brand milk . "
" I have to allow myself at least this much luxury . "
" And food for my precious fish , of course ... "
" May 12th . I was impressed with Eri Ochiai 's performance in Double Bind . "
" She 's another person when the camera is rolling ... "
What is all this ?
How do they know this much ?
Who are you ?
I 'm Dr. Toko Asamiya , specializing in psychiatry .
I was your late sister 's psychiatrist .
There are some things I 'd like to ask you .
Detective Yamashiro ! Another one !
What ! ?
This is the fifth victim ...
Just three shots .
Is this work really worth leaving CHAM for ?
Rumi . Do you know how hard it is to get a character ...
that reappears in a drama series ? Even a role like this ?
Yes , I do . But ...
This is where Mima proves if she can be seen as a real actress or not .
But we should sell Mima as a pop idol !
Really . Times are different from when Rumi Hidaka was a working pop idol .
I know that .
Nowadays , there are no places for pop idols to appeal to the masses .
This is the branch point that will decide if Mima lasts or not .
Well , excuse me for not surviving .
Please , Rumi !
There 's nothing better than having Mima be able to change into an actress !
She came to Tokyo to sing ...
Think !
On record sales we make practically nothing !
But I do wish that they 'd use her a little bit more ...
Sorry we 're not that profitable !
Good morning !
How 's the new CHAM going ?
Double Bind
It 's the pits !
Double Bind ... yeah , I saw it too .
It was so boring !
Why do all psycho-thrillers made in Japan turn out that way ?
Mimarin 's not in it !
Oh yeah . How many scenes was she in last week ? Four ?
Three .
Somebody save Mimarin ! PLEASE !
A HOME PAGE ON THE INTERNET : You can make one too !
This morning , when I got off the train left foot first ...
Hey , It 's Mimarin !
Good morning !
Good morning , Mimarin !
Break a leg with that drama series !
Hey , wait , Mimarin ...
Do they get all unfriendly when they become actresses ?
Hit-And-Run at Shinkaido .
Tadashi Doi ( 18 ) , in critical condition .
Good morning !
Good morning , Mima .
Cheers !
What 's going on ?
CHAM 's new single ...
Oh , wow ! They got 83rd ?
We never even made the charts before .
One , two ...
Congratulations !
We did it !
Now we 've got to work together really hard !
But will there be anyone in the audience ?
Sure there will be , Mima !
Your next script . It has a few more lines .
Yeah .
You 've both done great !
CHAM is totally okay being a duo !
Hey , you . Are you currently in any talent agency ?
I 'm sorry , I 'm in a hurry .
Hey !
Wouldn 't you be interested in being a model ?
Model ?
Cut !
OK ! We 're going to move for the next scene !
Who 's that girl ?
I don 't know .
Hey , hey , hey !
I saw next week 's script , Shibuya . You 're wonderful !
I didn 't think it would come to this !
To tell the truth , I have an even more drastic idea .
Fantastic !
But ...
I wonder if it would be all right for Mima ...
or rather , her agency .
Mima 's character , Yoko Takakura , changes ...
personalities completely when she 's raped by the customers at a strip show .
You 're crazy ! A rape scene ! ?
She 's the key figure in the second half of the series ! It 's an important role !
But Mima 's a pop idol !
Don 't worry , Mima .
We 'll ask the producer and get it changed .
Hey , hey . Wait a minute !
The scripts are already behind schedule as is , and the art staff is getting antsy !
How will it look if we make it worse by arguing ?
I even told Shibuya that she was changing out from a pop idol !
It 's our job to protect the celebrities in our agency !
There 's no way Mima can do such a thing !
It 's all right , Rumi .
I 'll do it .
Because I decided that I WILL become an actress .
Mima !
I see . You 're really wonderful , Mima !
This kind of thing is commonplace for actresses ! Jodie whatshername did it too !
Mima , please think it out .
Do you realize what will happen as a result of this ?
It 's not as if I 'm really getting raped !
Although ... I 'm sure my parents will flip when they see me like that .
Anyway , I 'll do it . I 'll give it my best shot .
Mima ...
I absolutely REFUSE to do it !
Well , Mr. Director ? How does the set look ?
I 'd prefer to shoot in a real club ...
but considering what we 're filming , nobody will let us shoot at their place .
Sheesh !
Please , I 'm counting on you .
Hey , hey , hey , come on , Yada !
What are you going to do with just the DATE of the next meeting ! ?
That doesn 't make for much of a meeting !
OK here !
We 're ready to shoot !
Scene 48 , " The manager gets dragged down " , take 1 !
Ten seconds ...
5 , 4 , 3 , 2 ...
Mmmm ! Looks good !
Ex-pop idols sure make a nice scene !
No ! Stop ! Let me go !
Cut it off ! Get off the stage !
Shut the fuck up !
Get out of here ! I 'll call the police !
You think I give a shit about cops ?
Stop !
Hands off !
Stop it !
Let me go ! Stop it !
Help ! Help me ! No !
Please ! NO !
Cut !
Hey , over there , hold your places !
OK ! Now move the cameras !
I 'm so sorry ...
Oh , no , it 's all right .
OK , next up , the rape scene !
Everyone , get ready !
Take 1 ! Rolling !
No ! Stop ! No ! No ! Stop !
Please ! Stop !
Cut !
No , no , no ! FASTER !
Sorry !
Once again , from the top !
No break yet ! Take 2 !
Please ! Stop !
No ! Please ! NO !
Stop it ! No !
Please !
Mimarin !
I 'm so tired !
Hey , where 's Rumi ?
Hmm ? Oh , she had a meeting to go to for me ...
Hey , Mima ...
You know ...
Nothing . You tried so hard ...
As a reward for your efforts , I 'll treat you to a delicious meal .
Lucky me !
I 'm home , fishies !
I wonder if you 're hungry yet ?
Of course I didn 't want to do it !
But I couldn 't trouble all the people who brought me this far !
See , didn 't I tell you ?
Is that the job that what you wanted ?
That was the PITS !
I don 't want to do that drama anymore !
The producer is a total pervert , and my role is really screwed up !
Singing in front of my fans has GOT to be the best for me after all !
Oh ... that scene ?
Of course I would be lying if I said I didn 't have any hesitations ...
but I looked at it as a hurdle I had to jump over as an actress .
I heard the ratings went up .
As always , the public at large are all idiots .
Yes . I 'd like to be recognized as an actress .
Not as " the ex-pop idol " ?
You got it !
I was fine coz Rei was always the one I liked .
I 'm sure all the Mimarin fans are crying right about now .
But CHAM did teach me a lot . It was a great experience in its own way .
Yeah , totally !
They 're probably whining , " That 's not Mimarin ! "
Mima 's Room
What was YOUR day like ?
" Today , I was still a little depressed ... "
" but receiving e-mail from all of you made me feel a little better . "
E-mail ?
" June 24 : Help me , everyone ... "
" Everyone is forcing me to do it ! It 's all the screenwriter 's fault ! "
Help ! Help ! Help ! Help ! Help ! Help !
This ... This isn 't true ! I 'm not writing any of this !
Of course ! The REAL Mima is writing this !
I know that deep down in your heart you want to be a pop idol again .
No !
I 'm no longer ...
No longer what ?
Oh , yeah , you 're no longer a pop idol .
You 're a filthy woman now .
Nobody likes idols with tarnished reputations !
That 's not true ! That 's not true !
Mimarin !
You can 't step back into that spotlight now ...
But that 's all right . I 'M here .
From now on , I 'll be in the light , and you 'll be in the shadows .
What are you saying ! ?
Who in the world are you ! ?
Nobody likes you anymore .
You 're tarnished ! FILTHY !
Stop ! Stop it !
I am not tarnished !
Wait !
WAIT !
Love makes your heart race .
If it means you 're loved in the end ...
be much more aggressive ...
because you will get a chance .
The angel of love smiles at you .
Is anyone there ?
Can you see the angel 's white wings ?
Or her eyes gazing at you ...
her sweet voice , her gentle hands ?
She is here just for you .
She is protecting you ...
from somewhere nearby .
Got a question about ...
Love makes your heart race .
If it means you 're loved in the end ...
be much more aggressive ...
It happened about 1 o 'clock this morning .
Hey , I called you last night and you weren 't in ...
" Oh shit ! How did you know ? " Yeah , right .
Did you see " Mima 's Room " ?
Yeah , but is that really her ?
No clue .
According to that page , Mimarin 's gonna be on stage today .
No way !
Police say Shibuya was stabbed umpteen times with a sharp object ...
Popular Script Writer SLAUGHTERED ! The victim : Takao Shibuya ( 34 ) Police say Shibuya was stabbed umpteen times with a sharp object ...
It sure is a shocking incident , but us worrying about it won 't help .
We have to put our minds on something else .
But there was that letter bomb too ...
You think Mr. Shibuya 's murder is connected with that ?
I didn 't say that ...
You watch too many TV tabloid shows . Don 't worry about it .
You won 't become a star looking like that ! Smile !
Shibuya won the New Writers ' Prize in 1990 , and then ...
Serves ...
you ...
right ! ?
What 's wrong ? Mima ! MIMA !
But will Mima be all right ?
Why ?
That photographer specializes in getting people to strip !
So what ?
She 's got that part down pat !
I 'm sure she 's totally showing it off in front of the photographer !
Like , TOTALLY !
Isn 't it time you were on ? Hurry up .
Yes 'm .
Oooh ... I like that expression .
Try running your fingers through your hair .
Oh , I like this .
It 's great !
Perfume isn 't for me . And when I caught the scent ...
Yeah , just like that . Part your lips a little ...
Great . Now let 's take the top off too ...
I 'd rather wear jeans ...
than tight business suits .
This year , I 'll not exert myself and dress casually .
I wanted to be a woman that suited you ...
but I knew we would drift apart even if ...
I kept standing on my tippy-toes .
I thought you decided to go through with this !
Everyone is waiting for you !
Come on , Mima !
See ? Didn 't I tell you ?
You were better off as a pop idol .
Hey Mima , are you listening ?
Stop all this nonsense ! Who are you ! ?
Me ? I 'm a pop idol .
Everyone 's waiting for me .
So I 'm going to sing with Rei and Yukiko again .
No , I 'm not !
I 'm an actress !
Don 't be silly !
No one really wants that !
Wait !
What everyone wants is ...
from comics than difficult books and ...
I want to stay the way I am forever .
Walking past , making a breeze ...
burning the scenery into my memories .
I am fine even if I 'm alone .
I have finally found a luxurious loneliness .
Thank you , everyone !
June 27th : Thank you for coming to the event today !
It really is the best feeling to sing in front of all of you !
BASTARDS !
Mima Kirigoe Leaving the Throne of a Pop Idol !
Huh ?
Hey !
What are you doing ?
To Mr. ME-MANIA : Thank you for your e-mail every day ...
You believe me , right ?
That 's not me . She 's an impostor !
Of course . Mimarin would never do such a thing .
I will protect you , the real Mimarin .
I trust you , Mr. ME-MANIA .
I won 't change one bit .
I 'll always be with you .
But that impostor keeps getting in my way .
What should I do ?
I 'll get rid of her .
Thank you , Mr. Me-mania !
You 're the only one I can depend on .
I don 't know anything about myself anymore !
Well ...
How do you think you know that person you were ...
a second ago is the same person you are now ?
A continuous stream of memories .
Given only that , we all create illusions within ourselves ...
saying that we each have only one fixed persona .
Doctor , I 'm scared ...
that my other self will do something that I don 't know about ...
It 's all right . There is no way illusions can come to life .
CUT !
Mima , what 's wrong ?
I 'm sorry !
Oh , man ! This rain sucks !
I think I 'm going to catch a cold !
I 'm sorry !
Wrap it up ! Wrap it up !
It 's pouring really badly outside , but your heart is always , like , sunny !
Well , I think we 're ready today !
Welcome to Rei ...
and Yukiko 's ...
" Idol Chamland " !
Mr. Tadokoro ?
I 'm sure they 're on the air now .
I thought you 'd like to see them coz it 's been a while .
We have a show this Sunday . It 's at Ibaragi Sim City at 2pm .
- How have you been ? - People from all over , come see us !
- Just thought I 'd drop by . - We 'll be waiting for you !
Chamland will be back next week at the same time . Until then ...
Two , three ...
Bye bye !
Good show , guys .
Hey , it 's Mima .
Mima !
Wait !
Who are you ! ?
I told you ! I 'M the real Mima .
In other news ...
Today , the Economic Planning Agency announced a " New Citizen 's Life Index " ...
that indicates the overall Japanese standard of living and ...
It feels like I haven 't seen you in a long time .
Well , I 've been busy too .
So , are you getting used to acting ?
Yeah .
It 's hard , but I chose to do it .
You 've matured quite a bit , Mima !
But it 's good that people seem to like the new Mima .
Yeah ...
That doesn 't look like a face that 's agreeing .
You know ... Mima ... Has someone been harassing you ?
I 've been visiting that home page .
It 's a bit much , even if it 's a complaint about how you changed your image ...
It 's better if you didn 't look at it .
Yeah ...
But maybe she is more like me than myself .
Mima ?
My other self that I buried deep within my heart .
What if ...
What if that other personality suddenly started acting on its own ?
It 's all right . There is no way illusions can come to life .
Rumi ?
CUT !
Mima ! What are you saying ?
I feel like I 'm gonna have nightmares about this line !
I 'm sorry !
What 's wrong ?
Uh , nothing ...
Once more , from the top ...
All right , Take 2 !
In other news ...
Today , the Economic Planning Agency announced a " New Citizen 's Life Index " ...
that indicates the overall Japanese standard of living and ...
It 's been a while , Rumi .
What ? I was here yesterday , too !
Yesterday ? Was that real ?
You 're weird , Mima .
Mima ! What 's wrong with you ! ?
You 're bleeding !
This blood is real , isn 't it ?
Mima !
Today I went shopping in Harajuku . I 'm a sucker for sale items .
I guess ... I went to Harajuku today ...
You mean ...
the murderer is an illusion she created ?
Yes .
She fears an imaginary security guard ...
and then doubles that figure with the serial murderer of top models .
But illusions don 't kill .
But ... what if that illusion found someone to possess ?
Possess ?
Then ... all those men who got murdered ?
Were those who were no longer of any use to her .
Find her quickly , Mr. Yamashiro .
Before another victim falls prey .
How much ?
You sure are a weird pizza man .
Stop ! Please stop !
Yeah , that looks good ... Come on , be more daring ! More passionate !
All right ! Take three !
- Hello ? - Mima ?
Are you all right over there ?
You haven 't heard yet ... about Mr. Murano ?
Can 't be !
Police say that Murano died of multiple stab wounds ...
Mr. Murano ! ? Really ! ?
We 're going crazy here !
Anyway , stay put until I get there . All right ! ?
The weapon used in the latest murder is said to closely resemble ...
the one used in last week 's killing of a popular screenwriter .
Police are considering a personal grudge as the motive ...
and are looking into connections between the two cases .
Miss Kirigoe ! Please , can we get your opinion about the murder of Mr. Murano ?
Do you know anything ?
Isn 't there a connection with the killing of Mr. Shibuya the screenwriter ?
Miss Kirigoe ! There are rumors of a love triangle ...
between you , Mr. Shibuya , and Mr. Murano and we ...
You think she 's jinxed ?
What happens twice happens thrice .
Let 's take bets on who 's next .
Cut it out !
Don 't mind them .
Am I alive ?
Maybe that truck hit me ... and this is all a dream ...
Everyone ready ?
OK . Mima !
Breathe harder than during rehearsal .
You 've just killed someone .
Yes .
And ... action !
Are you awake ?
You are ?
Can you tell me your name ?
Me ? I 'm Mima Kirigoe .
Okay . And what do you do ?
I 'm a pop idol ... no , an actress .
That must be hard work .
It 's hard , but it 's what I chose to do .
She thinks she 's a new young actress named Mima Kirigoe .
Dissociative Identity Disorder .
In other words , " multiple personality syndrome . "
All those crimes took place when she was some other persona .
So where 's the persona of the original Yoko ?
Yoko Takakura , the original persona ...
is nothing more than a character in a drama for her .
Being a " normal " girl ... how she was raped in a strip club ...
Everything happened as part of her drama series .
By doing so , she salvaged her heart .
That 's right . I 'm an actress .
Cut !
Can you tell me your name ?
Me ? I 'm Rika Takakura .
The original persona , Yoko Takakura , no longer exists .
By killing , and later becoming , her sister the top-model , she salvaged her heart .
That 's right . I 'm a model .
All right ! That 's the take !
We did it , Mima !
Mima ... Good work !
I can tell you tried so hard !
Rumi ...
As of this moment , Double Bind is in the can !
Everyone , great job !
You were fantastic , Mima ! What do you think , Director ?
She really was excellent .
Thanks a lot .
See you at the wrap-up party .
We 'll be talking to you .
Then ... shall we go as well ?
Mima , go get changed .
Dr. Touko ...
Hey now ! I 'm not Touko anymore ! Did you forget ?
" There is no way illusions can come to life . "
You should stop dreaming soon .
Eri ?
What 's taking Mima so long ?
I 'm going back to the office . Take Mima home , will ya ?
Mr. Tadokoro . You were saying something about Mima 's next job ?
Oh , it 's great !
A starring role in a video movie .
There are a few sketchy scenes ... but what can you do ?
Somebody help me !
Like anyone can hear YOUR voice right now !
Who are you ! ?
Why are you doing this ! ?
I 'm protecting my dear Mimarin !
But-But I 'm Mima !
No , no , no , no , NO !
You didn 't know I was Me-mania !
You 're just PRETENDING to be Mimarin !
STOP !
NO ! STOP !
Did you fool that screenwriter and that photographer with this little mouth ?
You tarnished Mimarin 's name !
Can it be ... that you ...
The real Mimarin e-mails me every day !
And she says that you keep getting in her way !
You killed them ! ?
And you 'll die soon , too !
Bad girl !
You have to follow the script !
And now ... TAKE 2 !
All right ! Looks good !
You 're the best , Mima !
Mima !
What 's wrong ? You 're in shambles !
I was looking all over for you !
Rumi ...
What in the world happened ?
This can 't be !
Are you sure you weren 't dreaming ?
Are you all right ?
I 'm taking you back ... to Mima 's room .
Rumi , are you here ?
What ?
Oh , nothing ...
Oh , that 's right , I have to call Mr. Tadokoro .
No ... This isn 't my room ...
Of course not ! This is Mima 's room !
You 're !
Look ! It 's the new costume !
I 'm wearing it at tomorrow 's show !
Isn 't it great ? It 's perfect on me !
Rumi ? Why ?
Rumi ?
Rumi ...
Oh ! Rumi went home .
She said she 's been busy lately and was deprived of sleep .
Don 't say weird stuff like that !
This is a joke , isn 't it , Rumi ! ?
Love makes your heart race .
If it means you 're loved in the end ...
What do you think ? Perfect , huh ?
A pop idol HAS to sing , after all !
But ...
You just had to keep getting in my way .
Rumi was totally furious , too .
Please ... stop all of this !
But a pop idol is always protected by her fans !
They listen to any favor I , Mima , ask them !
Although Mr. Me-mania failed a wee bit ...
Me-mania ? How do you know him ! ?
But , oh , well ... " you reap what you sow , " especially about YOU .
Help ! Somebody help me !
Please ! Rumi , it 's you , isn 't it ! ?
PLEASE WAKE UP !
YOU 'RE the one who needs to wake up !
Help , help , somebody !
Help ! SOMEBODY HELP ME !
SOMEBODY ! SOMEBODY HELP ME !
HELP ! SOMEBODY HELP ME !
Let 's end all of this .
We don 't need two Mimas !
I AM MIMA !
That 's funny ! Mima is a pop idol !
You 're just a dirty old impostor !
LIKE I CARE ! I AM WHO I AM !
Oh , shit !
Get the police ! No , call an ambulance !
I know !
Thank you for the flowers you always bring .
I 'll put them in my room .
They 're pretty . Very pretty ...
I didn 't know you were visiting . You must be very busy lately .
Oh , no .
Once in a while , she returns to her Rumi persona , but ...
I know I 'll never see HER ever again .
But , thanks to her , I am who I am today .
You 're lying ! There 's no way Mima Kirigoe would be HERE of all places !
I guess she was just a look-alike .
No , I 'm real !
Each time I pass this station on the train ...
my heart fills with nostalgia .
The days when I ran around town , hiding all of my feelings ...
in my school uniform .
Take me to the first time I was in love ...
those four seasons when I was frantic yet doubtful .
Remember all those times when just being near each other ...
kept our love for each other growing ?
I cut my hair after graduation .
I wonder if you are still the same .
Are you still pursuing that dream that you kept telling me about ...
on the way home ?
Take me to when my tears overflowed ...
to those four seasons that I felt from the bottom of my heart .
Remember how in the sunsets after school ...
we just wanted time to spend alone ?
Even in this new season , I can 't shake ...
the habit of bluffing when I am sad .
I 'm sure that you knew .
I still remember your eyes when you looked at me silently .